<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:webfeeds="http://webfeeds.org/rss/1.0">
  <channel>
    <title>About on Response Ready Inc.</title>
    <link>https://responsereadyinc.ca/</link>
    <description>Recent content in About on Response Ready Inc.</description><webfeeds:icon>https://responsereadyinc.ca/favicon.ico</webfeeds:icon>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
    <atom:link href="https://responsereadyinc.ca/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>AED Sale</title>
      <link>https://responsereadyinc.ca/aed/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://responsereadyinc.ca/aed/</guid>
      
        <description>Heart Start Onsite HS1 Defibrillator Designed for the ordinary person in the extraordinary moment, Philips HeartStart HS1 AED is ready to act and virtually ready to go. It allows anyone with little or no training to treat the most common cause of suspected sudden cardiac arrest (SCA) by delivering a shock quickly and effectively, wherever SCA happens. The HS1 AED provides practically real-time guidance through step-by-step voice commands from pad placement to performing CPR.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://responsereadyinc.ca/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://responsereadyinc.ca/contact/</guid>
      
        <description>Response Ready/Intervention Rapide Inc.
Steve – 204-880-8360
Andre – 204-297-7431
email</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Staff Portfolios</title>
      <link>https://responsereadyinc.ca/staff/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://responsereadyinc.ca/staff/</guid>
      
        <description>Steve Brglez is an owner / operator of Response Ready Inc. providing Emergency Response / CPR training throughout Manitoba. Steve has worked for the Winnipeg Fire Paramedic Service as an Advanced Care Paramedic for 15 years in numerous capacities including with the Winnipeg Police Tactical Emergency Medical Services Unit and as a Community Paramedic. He currently operates as a District Chief of Paramedic Operations for WFPS. He has a desire to teach and provide quality emergency training to the citizens of Manitoba.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stop the Bleed</title>
      <link>https://responsereadyinc.ca/stopthebleed/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://responsereadyinc.ca/stopthebleed/</guid>
      
        <description>Hemorrhage Control stopthebleed.org and Bleeding Control Kits® provide the tools and information you need to act quickly to stop traumatic blood loss.
Public Access Bleeding Control Kits are designed for use by medical professionals, first responders and general citizens in serious trauma emergencies. A fast response along with an easy, recognizable access to equipment is imperative to &amp;ldquo;Stop the Bleed&amp;rdquo;. Response Ready Inc. is your trainer and distributor of the bleeding control kits, which through public education will be as prevalent as public AED&amp;rsquo;s, in serving a vital purpose in the preservation of life in the emergency bleeding scenario.</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
